export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2009 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0812q.pdf",
        solution: "0901a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Khaled Halaoua", affiliation: "ISSAT, Syria" },
            { name: "Brian Bradie", affiliation: "Christopher Newport University, VA, USA" },
            { name: "Lo Giudice Alessio", affiliation: "University of Palermo, Italy" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science and Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Salvaggio Andrea", affiliation: "University of Palermo, Italy" },
            { name: "Juergen Weith", affiliation: "University of Applied Sciences, Schweinfurt, Germany" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0901q.pdf",
        solution: "0902a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Manh Dung Nguyen", affiliation: "High school for gifted students, HUS, Vietnam" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Ilias Giechaskiel", affiliation: "Anatolia College, Thessaloniki, Greece" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Mohsen Sujadi nia", affiliation: "Agriculture University of Iran" },
            { name: "Can Gokler", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0902q.pdf",
        solution: "0903a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Manh Dung Nguyen", affiliation: "High school for gifted students, HUS, Vietnam" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Abhishek Verma", affiliation: "Delhi College of Engineering, India" },
            { name: "Michel Bataille", affiliation: "Rouen, France" },
            { name: "Tuan Le", affiliation: "Fairmont High School, Anaheim, CA, USA" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science and Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Can Gokler", affiliation: "METU" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0903q.pdf",
        solution: "0904a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong-Kong, China" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Cao Minh Quang", affiliation: "Nguyen Binh Khiem High School, Vinh Long, Vietnam" },
            { name: "Andrea Munaro", affiliation: "University of Trento, Italy" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "M. Haluk Guler", affiliation: "University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, USA" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Tuan Le", affiliation: "Fairmont High School, Anaheim, CA, USA" },
            { name: "Manh Dung Nguyen", affiliation: "High school for gifted students, HUS, Vietnam" },
            { name: "Abhishek Verma", affiliation: "Delhi College of Engineering, India" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "Devlet Malzeme Ofisi, Istanbul" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0904q.pdf",
        solution: "0905a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science and Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong-Kong, China" },
            { name: "Stanislav Volkov", affiliation: "Mittag-Leffler Institute, Sweden" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Hachem Hadi", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science and Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Boukharfane Radouan", affiliation: "Moulay Driss FES, Morocco" },
            { name: "Abhishek Verma", affiliation: "Delhi College of Engineering, India" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0905q.pdf",
        solution: "0906a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Boukharfane Radouane", affiliation: "Moulay Driss FES, Morocco" },
            { name: "Cuneyd Ozturk", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Aslihan Demirkaya", affiliation: "University of Kansas, USA" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong-Kong, China" },
            { name: "Gorkem Ozkaya", affiliation: "Princeton University, USA" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Tuan Le", affiliation: "Fairmont High School, Anaheim, CA, USA" },
            { name: "Konstantine Zelator", affiliation: "Rhode Island College, R.I., USA" },
            { name: "Ruben Victor Cohen", affiliation: "Buenos Aires, Argentina" },
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0906q.pdf",
        solution: "0908a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science and Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong-Kong, China" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Peng Chhay Ung", affiliation: "Lycee Fenelon in Paris, France" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Fatma Topuz", affiliation: "Dumlupinar University, Kutahya" },
            { name: "Cuneyd Ozturk", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mithil Ramteke", affiliation: "Bangalore, India" },
            { name: "Can Turkun", affiliation: "TOBB University, Ankara" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0908q.pdf",
        solution: "0909a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Bahadir Gizlici", affiliation: "Yeditepe University, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong-Kong, China" },
            { name: "Boukharfane Radouane", affiliation: "ISAE, Toulouse, France" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Samil Akcagil", affiliation: "Sakarya University" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "Bursa Ozel Nilufer Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Naser Pastoriza Alejandro Jose", affiliation: "FaMAF-Unc.-Cordoba, Argentina" },
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Khaled Halaoua", affiliation: "ISSAT, Damascus, Syria" },
            { name: "Cuneyd Ozturk", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ghalem Allai", affiliation: "Supaero ISAE, France" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Ali Sari", affiliation: "Yildiz Teknik University" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0909q.pdf",
        solution: "0910a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Chuan Guo", affiliation: "University of Waterloo, Canada" },
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science and Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Idoughi Ramzi", affiliation: "Supaero ISAE, Toulouse, France" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0910q.pdf",
        solution: "0911a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "Bursa Ozel Nilufer Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ernist Elmar Tilenbaev", affiliation: "TOBB University" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Bekjan Djumabaev", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2009,
        question: "0911q.pdf",
        solution: "0912a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
            { name: "Can Turkun", affiliation: "TOBB University" },
            { name: "Omran Kouba", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
            { name: "Tran Thanh Nam", affiliation: "Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Marco Figueroa", affiliation: "Guanajuato University, Mexico" },
            { name: "Ilias Giechaskiel", affiliation: "Princeton University" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Harald Bogeholz", affiliation: "c't Computer magazine, Germany" },
            { name: "Andreas Stiller", affiliation: "c't Computer magazine, Germany" },
            { name: "Cornel Gruian", affiliation: "SC Remarul, Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
            { name: "Ali Kemal Uncu", affiliation: "TOBB University" },
            { name: "F. Wallner", affiliation: "Munich, Germany" }
        ]
    }
];
